{
  "questions": [
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(1 > \\dfrac{-16}{15}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{59}{33} \\div \\dfrac{-11}{70}\\)",
      "answer": "-4130/363",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        363
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert -1.263 &times; 10<sup>5</sup> to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "-126300",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert 0.1007 to standard form",
      "answer": "1.007e-1",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "stdf"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(5.2 \\leq 0.048\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{97}{51} - \\dfrac{-71}{99}\\)",
      "answer": "4408/1683",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1683
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{47}{20} + \\dfrac{9}{17}\\)",
      "answer": "979/340",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        340
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{30} \\div 8.6\\)",
      "answer": "7/258",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        258
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{55}{4} \\div 76\\)",
      "answer": "55/304",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        304
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{48}{97} \\div 0.045\\)",
      "answer": "3200/291",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        291
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(37 \\div \\dfrac{6}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "481/6",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        6
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-4.6 - 0.1\\)",
      "answer": "-47/10",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        10
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{33}{28} \\div \\dfrac{-7}{31}\\)",
      "answer": "-1023/196",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        196
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{97}{67} > \\dfrac{12}{31}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{71}{96}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "357911/884736",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        884736
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{7} \\div -5.2\\)",
      "answer": "-55/182",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        182
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\((-4.1071)^{-1}\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "-0.24",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDps": [
        2
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.038 \\geq 5.2\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.037\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1369/1000000",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1000000
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{28}{43} > \\dfrac{11}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{91}{93} < 0.062\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7 + \\dfrac{49}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "105/8",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        8
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\((-431.6)^{-1}\\) to 4 decimal places",
      "answer": "-0.0023",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDps": [
        4
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert 259000 to standard form",
      "answer": "2.59e5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "stdf"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{92}{85} \\div \\dfrac{82}{57}\\)",
      "answer": "2622/3485",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        3485
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-87\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-658503",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{71}{88} \\div \\dfrac{49}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "355/4312",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        4312
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.027 \\div \\dfrac{83}{65}\\)",
      "answer": "351/16600",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        16600
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{35}{48}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-35/48",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        48
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{49}{38} \\div -0.2\\)",
      "answer": "-245/38",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        38
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{87}{71}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "658503/357911",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        357911
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{23}{29} + \\dfrac{17}{45}\\)",
      "answer": "1528/1305",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1305
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{34}{3}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "39304/27",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        27
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(49\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "117649",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(2.8 \\geq \\dfrac{13}{33}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{23}{9} + \\dfrac{26}{31}\\)",
      "answer": "947/279",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        279
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.095 - \\dfrac{-64}{23}\\)",
      "answer": "12363/4600",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        4600
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{23}{72} + -34\\)",
      "answer": "-2425/72",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        72
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert 2.77 &times; 10<sup>5</sup> to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "277000",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert 0.01327 to standard form",
      "answer": "1.327e-2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "stdf"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.85 \\leq \\dfrac{7}{23}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(-7.5 > \\dfrac{11}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-91 \\div \\dfrac{15}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "-1001/15",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        15
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{12} < \\dfrac{-35}{83}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{40} = \\dfrac{85}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{22}{89} \\div \\dfrac{68}{59}\\)",
      "answer": "649/3026",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        3026
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.014\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "343/125000000",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        125000000
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-31}{33} + \\dfrac{15}{47}\\)",
      "answer": "-962/1551",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1551
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.068 \\div -22\\)",
      "answer": "-17/5500",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        5500
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.012 - \\dfrac{68}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "-16961/3250",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        3250
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-72}{91} \\div \\dfrac{61}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "-72/793",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        793
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(7.3\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "5329/100",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        100
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{19}{10} \\div \\dfrac{31}{28}\\)",
      "answer": "266/155",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        155
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{12}{61} - \\dfrac{5}{2}\\)",
      "answer": "-281/122",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        122
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{17} \\div \\dfrac{-64}{87}\\)",
      "answer": "-261/1088",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1088
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.32 - \\dfrac{-5}{12}\\)",
      "answer": "221/300",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        300
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.61 - \\dfrac{56}{85}\\)",
      "answer": "-83/1700",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1700
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-11}{10}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "121/100",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        100
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{49}{40} > 0.034\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(24 - \\dfrac{18}{61}\\)",
      "answer": "1446/61",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        61
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{19}{36}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "361/1296",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1296
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{71}{99} \\div \\dfrac{49}{94}\\)",
      "answer": "6674/4851",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        4851
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{71} > \\dfrac{1}{80}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert 1.51 &times; 10<sup>5</sup> to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "151000",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.026 + \\dfrac{35}{52}\\)",
      "answer": "1136/1625",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1625
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-2 + 35\\)",
      "answer": "33",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{44}{43} \\div \\dfrac{23}{21}\\)",
      "answer": "924/989",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        989
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.78 - -6\\)",
      "answer": "339/50",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        50
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(7.914^{-1}\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.126",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDps": [
        3
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-2}{7} - -75\\)",
      "answer": "523/7",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        7
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{39}{46}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-39/46",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        46
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{24}{23} \\geq 5\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.42^{-1}\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "2.381",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDps": [
        3
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert -88700 to standard form",
      "answer": "-8.87e4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "stdf"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{85}{64} \\div \\dfrac{23}{33}\\)",
      "answer": "2805/1472",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1472
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-6}{47} \\div 0.61\\)",
      "answer": "-600/2867",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        2867
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{44}{35} + -2.5\\)",
      "answer": "-87/70",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        70
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.83 \\div \\dfrac{37}{49}\\)",
      "answer": "-4067/3700",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        3700
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.5 \\div \\dfrac{82}{89}\\)",
      "answer": "89/164",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        164
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{67}{70} - -35\\)",
      "answer": "2517/70",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        70
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{58}{71} + 0\\)",
      "answer": "58/71",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        71
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{49}{55}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "2401/3025",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        3025
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(51.06^{1.5}\\) to 4 decimal places",
      "answer": "364.8558",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDps": [
        4
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{27}{23} + 6.7\\)",
      "answer": "1811/230",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        230
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{63}{55} \\div \\dfrac{-2}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-189/110",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        110
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{4}{39} - \\dfrac{5}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "-179/156",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        156
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(6.3\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-63/10",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        10
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{83}{49} \\geq \\dfrac{37}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{3} < 12\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{3} + \\dfrac{4}{35}\\)",
      "answer": "47/105",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        105
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{81}{97} \\geq 98\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.092 - \\dfrac{-40}{63}\\)",
      "answer": "11449/15750",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        15750
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{31}{35} \\div 0\\)",
      "answer": "undefined",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": []
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{8}{49} \\div 16\\)",
      "answer": "1/98",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        98
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{49}{54} \\div -0.074\\)",
      "answer": "-12250/999",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        999
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{20}{47} \\div \\dfrac{79}{27}\\)",
      "answer": "540/3713",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        3713
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert -1.289 &times; 10<sup>6</sup> to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "-1289000",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-50}{11} \\div 0.19\\)",
      "answer": "-5000/209",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        209
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{66}{59}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-66/59",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        59
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{37}{24} + \\dfrac{83}{25}\\)",
      "answer": "2917/600",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        600
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.093\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "8649/1000000",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1000000
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-2}{3} \\div 0.86\\)",
      "answer": "-100/129",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        129
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{55}{19} \\div \\dfrac{-27}{53}\\)",
      "answer": "-2915/513",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        513
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{38}{5} - 8.4\\)",
      "answer": "-4/5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        5
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7.9 - \\dfrac{19}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "63/20",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        20
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.084\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "441/62500",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        62500
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{26}{37} \\div \\dfrac{95}{91}\\)",
      "answer": "2366/3515",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        3515
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{53}{3}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "2809/9",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        9
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-83}{92} - \\dfrac{-10}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "173/828",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        828
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert 1.249 &times; 10<sup>6</sup> to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "1249000",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.7083^{0.5}\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.842",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDps": [
        3
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(7.4 > 41\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(8.9 > -0.01\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{23} \\div \\dfrac{70}{79}\\)",
      "answer": "79/1610",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1610
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{81}{92} \\geq \\dfrac{89}{91}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{39}{50} \\div \\dfrac{51}{29}\\)",
      "answer": "377/850",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        850
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{86}{53} \\div -0.065\\)",
      "answer": "-17200/689",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        689
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-9.3 \\div 0.038\\)",
      "answer": "-4650/19",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        19
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-17 - 11\\)",
      "answer": "-28",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.8534^{1.5}\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.788",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDps": [
        3
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{14}{3} - 0.95\\)",
      "answer": "223/60",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        60
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{17}{18} \\div 66\\)",
      "answer": "17/1188",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1188
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-32}{17} - \\dfrac{5}{47}\\)",
      "answer": "-1589/799",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        799
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{94}{65} - 0.039\\)",
      "answer": "18293/13000",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        13000
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.019 - \\dfrac{33}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "-8231/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1000
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{80}{69} \\geq \\dfrac{51}{64}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-14}{3} \\div 0.71\\)",
      "answer": "-1400/213",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        213
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{27}{13} \\div \\dfrac{3}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "72/13",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        13
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{79} < \\dfrac{9}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{91}{4} + \\dfrac{81}{23}\\)",
      "answer": "2417/92",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        92
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-73}{86} \\div \\dfrac{9}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "-511/774",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        774
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.89^{-1}\\) to 4 decimal places",
      "answer": "1.1236",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDps": [
        4
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.78 \\leq \\dfrac{77}{59}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert -17.91 to standard form",
      "answer": "-1.791e1",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "stdf"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{9}{68} \\div 4.9\\)",
      "answer": "45/1666",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1666
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{37}{40} + 0.09\\)",
      "answer": "203/200",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        200
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.89 = \\dfrac{13}{72}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(72\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-72",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{10} \\div \\dfrac{-29}{62}\\)",
      "answer": "-31/145",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        145
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{24}{73} + \\dfrac{13}{29}\\)",
      "answer": "1645/2117",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        2117
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-47}{36} \\geq 0.81\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert -10330 to standard form",
      "answer": "-1.033e4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "stdf"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(20\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-20",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(4.6\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "12167/125",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        125
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{15}{73} - 91\\)",
      "answer": "-6628/73",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        73
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{15}{4}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "3375/64",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        64
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4.2 + \\dfrac{7}{74}\\)",
      "answer": "1589/370",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        370
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{65} \\leq \\dfrac{-10}{17}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{13}{9} \\div \\dfrac{1}{61}\\)",
      "answer": "793/9",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        9
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-38}{31} \\geq 6.5\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.24 > 8\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{13}{33}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "2197/35937",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        35937
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{43}{27}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "1849/729",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        729
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(2 \\div \\dfrac{1}{29}\\)",
      "answer": "58",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.095 + \\dfrac{27}{8}\\)",
      "answer": "347/100",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        100
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{83}{63} \\div 5\\)",
      "answer": "83/315",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        315
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.013 \\div \\dfrac{65}{14}\\)",
      "answer": "-7/2500",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        2500
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(-0.94 \\geq \\dfrac{5}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{31} - 3.6\\)",
      "answer": "-563/155",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        155
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-57}{92} \\div 0.05\\)",
      "answer": "-285/23",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        23
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{36}{29} \\leq 8.2\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{83}{11} \\div 8.7\\)",
      "answer": "830/957",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        957
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{11} - \\dfrac{-43}{72}\\)",
      "answer": "977/792",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        792
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{49} - 0.033\\)",
      "answer": "-617/49000",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        49000
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.034 \\div 0.047\\)",
      "answer": "34/47",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        47
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-71 \\div \\dfrac{7}{22}\\)",
      "answer": "-1562/7",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        7
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert 0.097 to standard form",
      "answer": "9.7e-2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "stdf"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.05 + \\dfrac{34}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "137/20",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        20
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8 \\div 3.4\\)",
      "answer": "40/17",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        17
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(4 + \\dfrac{30}{83}\\)",
      "answer": "362/83",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        83
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{57}{5} - 30\\)",
      "answer": "-93/5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        5
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{29}{93} - \\dfrac{97}{55}\\)",
      "answer": "-7426/5115",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        5115
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{21}{16} + \\dfrac{-2}{95}\\)",
      "answer": "1963/1520",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1520
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-39}{56} - 88\\)",
      "answer": "-4967/56",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        56
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{14}{15} + \\dfrac{18}{37}\\)",
      "answer": "788/555",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        555
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(0.53\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-53/100",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        100
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.058 \\div \\dfrac{62}{15}\\)",
      "answer": "87/6200",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        6200
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.048 - \\dfrac{12}{37}\\)",
      "answer": "-1722/4625",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        4625
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(4.7 = \\dfrac{47}{58}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.78 \\div \\dfrac{-25}{24}\\)",
      "answer": "-468/625",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        625
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0 + -19\\)",
      "answer": "-19",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{80}{27} + 0\\)",
      "answer": "80/27",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        27
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{23}{14}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "529/196",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        196
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert -1.121 &times; 10<sup>2</sup> to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "-112.1",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.18\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "81/2500",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        2500
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{5} < \\dfrac{-5}{44}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(5.1896^{1.5}\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "11.82",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDps": [
        2
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-0.028\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "49/62500",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        62500
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{17} \\div 7.9\\)",
      "answer": "50/1343",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1343
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.11 + 0.19\\)",
      "answer": "3/10",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        10
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.058 + -9.2\\)",
      "answer": "-4571/500",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        500
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.029 \\div \\dfrac{-8}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "-261/8000",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        8000
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{47}{92} + -3.2\\)",
      "answer": "-1237/460",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        460
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{77}{10} \\geq 0.94\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{45}{28} \\div \\dfrac{21}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "75/196",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        196
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7 \\div \\dfrac{58}{97}\\)",
      "answer": "679/58",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        58
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert 0.00359 to standard form",
      "answer": "3.59e-3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "stdf"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{4}{7} \\div 1\\)",
      "answer": "4/7",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        7
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(8.372^{-0.5}\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.35",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDps": [
        2
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(9.1\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-91/10",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        10
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-68}{33}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-314432/35937",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        35937
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7 - \\dfrac{7}{20}\\)",
      "answer": "133/20",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        20
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{21}{4} - 0.46\\)",
      "answer": "479/100",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        100
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(0.59^{0.5}\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.768",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDps": [
        3
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{2} - 0.079\\)",
      "answer": "-579/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1000
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{73}{57} \\div \\dfrac{29}{37}\\)",
      "answer": "2701/1653",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1653
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{38}{23} \\div -0.057\\)",
      "answer": "-2000/69",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        69
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{92}{11} + \\dfrac{48}{71}\\)",
      "answer": "7060/781",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        781
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{13}{92} \\div 81\\)",
      "answer": "13/7452",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        7452
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.058 \\div \\dfrac{91}{51}\\)",
      "answer": "1479/45500",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        45500
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(56.0^{-1}\\) to 4 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.0179",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDps": [
        4
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(7.8 + 38\\)",
      "answer": "229/5",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        5
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{47}{80} - \\dfrac{65}{89}\\)",
      "answer": "-1017/7120",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        7120
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{11}{19} \\div \\dfrac{-99}{47}\\)",
      "answer": "-47/171",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        171
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert 1.157 to standard form",
      "answer": "1.157e0",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "stdf"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{47}{37} \\div \\dfrac{-61}{85}\\)",
      "answer": "-3995/2257",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        2257
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-29}{52}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "841/2704",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        2704
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-6}{49}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "36/2401",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        2401
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{9}{10}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "729/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1000
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{24}{41} \\div -70\\)",
      "answer": "-12/1435",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1435
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.56 \\div \\dfrac{-65}{87}\\)",
      "answer": "-1218/1625",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1625
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-12}{5} + 0.037\\)",
      "answer": "-2363/1000",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1000
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-1}{56}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-1/175616",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        175616
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(-4.7 > \\dfrac{13}{74}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-80}{51} = \\dfrac{85}{14}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(0.95\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "361/400",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        400
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{65}{47} - -0.048\\)",
      "answer": "8407/5875",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        5875
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert 1.459 &times; 10<sup>2</sup> to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "145.9",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert 135.7 to standard form",
      "answer": "1.357e2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "stdf"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert 1.587 &times; 10<sup>-1</sup> to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "0.1587",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{41}{86}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "68921/636056",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        636056
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert 0.391 to standard form",
      "answer": "3.91e-1",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "stdf"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{10} - 0.8\\)",
      "answer": "-1/2",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        2
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{-2}{23}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "-8/12167",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        12167
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{55}{24}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "166375/13824",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        13824
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.057 \\div \\dfrac{-50}{81}\\)",
      "answer": "-4617/50000",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        50000
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{95}{52} < \\dfrac{41}{79}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-34}{15} \\div 78\\)",
      "answer": "-17/585",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        585
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert -8670 to standard form",
      "answer": "-8.67e3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "stdf"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{28}{87} - \\dfrac{58}{69}\\)",
      "answer": "-346/667",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        667
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{87}{25} - \\dfrac{87}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "-1827/100",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        100
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{86} \\div \\dfrac{46}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "-7/3956",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        3956
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(-0.015\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "3/200",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        200
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.044 - 0.89\\)",
      "answer": "-423/500",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        500
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{13}{7} + \\dfrac{29}{98}\\)",
      "answer": "211/98",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        98
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{84}{61} \\div 0.092\\)",
      "answer": "21000/1403",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1403
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{44} + 0.6\\)",
      "answer": "157/220",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        220
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{83}{59} - \\dfrac{21}{11}\\)",
      "answer": "-326/649",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        649
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5.5 - \\dfrac{11}{35}\\)",
      "answer": "363/70",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        70
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(-47\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "2209",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.064 - \\dfrac{1}{16}\\)",
      "answer": "3/2000",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        2000
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-53}{64} + \\dfrac{-1}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "-297/320",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        320
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-25}{99} \\div \\dfrac{75}{88}\\)",
      "answer": "-8/27",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        27
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3 + \\dfrac{67}{57}\\)",
      "answer": "238/57",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        57
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-75}{2} \\div 0.032\\)",
      "answer": "-9375/8",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        8
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{17}{16} \\geq \\dfrac{77}{40}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(9.2995^{0.5}\\) to 4 decimal places",
      "answer": "3.0495",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDps": [
        4
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{7}{10} + \\dfrac{-2}{9}\\)",
      "answer": "43/90",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        90
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{13}{19} - -6.4\\)",
      "answer": "673/95",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        95
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{99}{82}\\right)^{2}\\)",
      "answer": "9801/6724",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        6724
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-21}{71} - \\dfrac{98}{43}\\)",
      "answer": "-7861/3053",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        3053
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(42 + 4.9\\)",
      "answer": "469/10",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        10
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(0.25 \\geq \\dfrac{6}{7}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.001 \\div \\dfrac{7}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "13/7000",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        7000
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{31} \\div 58\\)",
      "answer": "1/1798",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1798
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-7.9 - \\dfrac{36}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "-1387/130",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        130
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(1 \\div \\dfrac{1}{67}\\)",
      "answer": "67",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert 1.769 &times; 10<sup>5</sup> to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "176900",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{10}{3} - \\dfrac{1}{13}\\)",
      "answer": "127/39",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        39
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{5}{47} \\div \\dfrac{9}{4}\\)",
      "answer": "20/423",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        423
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(\\dfrac{-3}{10}\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "3/10",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        10
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-1}{6} - \\dfrac{30}{97}\\)",
      "answer": "-277/582",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        582
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{3}{4} < \\dfrac{57}{10}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(8 + -93\\)",
      "answer": "-85",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(94 \\div 8.1\\)",
      "answer": "940/81",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        81
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-61}{84} \\geq \\dfrac{-4}{55}\\)",
      "answer": "1",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{46}{47} \\div \\dfrac{43}{6}\\)",
      "answer": "276/2021",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        2021
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-53}{9} - 8\\)",
      "answer": "-125/9",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        9
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.024 \\div \\dfrac{16}{61}\\)",
      "answer": "183/2000",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        2000
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert 5.83 &times; 10<sup>-3</sup> to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "0.00583",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(5 \\div \\dfrac{5}{3}\\)",
      "answer": "3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{-19}{5} \\div \\dfrac{38}{47}\\)",
      "answer": "-47/10",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        10
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert 1.153 &times; 10<sup>-1</sup> to decimal expansion",
      "answer": "0.1153",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert -4570 to standard form",
      "answer": "-4.57e3",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "stdf"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.066 \\div 9.3\\)",
      "answer": "11/1550",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1550
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\((-0.2098)^{-1}\\) to 3 decimal places",
      "answer": "-4.766",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDps": [
        3
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(0.042 + \\dfrac{5}{43}\\)",
      "answer": "3403/21500",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        21500
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{24}{7} - \\dfrac{43}{36}\\)",
      "answer": "563/252",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        252
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-0.49 + \\dfrac{43}{40}\\)",
      "answer": "117/200",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        200
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(3 \\div -0.97\\)",
      "answer": "-300/97",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        97
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{41}{46} \\geq -0.002\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{72}{65} \\leq \\dfrac{61}{19}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{8}{31} + 0.022\\)",
      "answer": "4341/15500",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        15500
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "mcq",
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{1}{14} \\leq \\dfrac{32}{21}\\)",
      "answer": "0",
      "choices": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{63}{13} \\div \\dfrac{46}{91}\\)",
      "answer": "441/46",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        46
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(-\\left(0.45\\right)\\)",
      "answer": "-9/20",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec",
        "mix",
        "cfr"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        20
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\left(\\dfrac{95}{9}\\right)^{3}\\)",
      "answer": "857375/729",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        729
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Convert 0.00041 to standard form",
      "answer": "4.1e-4",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "stdf"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Round \\(91.0^{-1}\\) to 2 decimal places",
      "answer": "0.01",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDps": [
        2
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\dfrac{46}{5} \\div \\dfrac{1}{5}\\)",
      "answer": "46",
      "numberInputTypes": [
        "cfr",
        "mix",
        "dec"
      ],
      "expectedDenominators": [
        0,
        1
      ]
    }
  ]
}
